Battle for the Red Stone of Asia,
JoJo versus Wamuu in a
one-on-one chariot duel!
The time is upon us.
When the full moon once again emerges from
behind that cloud, the battle will begin!
I wish they wouldn't make all that noise?
Why is it that the bad
guys get all the fans?
One lap is 960 meters.
It takes approximately one minute
for these beasts to complete a lap.
Do you see that column over there?
On each lap a different weapon
will be hanging from it.
Weapons.
No one.
Weapon at at a time.
Whichever of us can capture
that column before the
other will then have the
opportunity to wield the weapon.
Do you see the first one up there?
It's a giant sledgehammer.
That thing could smash right
through a chariot in one blow.
If wamuu was able to get his hands on it,
my situation isn't just going to be bad?
it could be terminal.
But if I can get to it first,
cover it with oil and fill it with
Hamon, then victory will be mine.
I am looking forward to an excellent,
fulfilling fight from you, Jojo. Get ready.
The moon approaches the cloud's edge.
When its light falls upon
us, the contest begins.
Jojo, what are you doing there?
The race is about to start.
I'm well aware of that.
The start will be the key, and I
sure don't want to mess that up.
That's why I'm checking
the rubble under my wheels.
Look at that, Wamuu.
You've got quite a big
pile under your buggy.
Are you going to take care of it?
Hurry!
Come on, get's up there!
Jojo!
Begin now!
Thank you.
Hi-yah!
What's this now?
Lord Wabu is having trouble!
His chariot is just standing there!
Look at that, his wheels are blocked.
Jojo, he did this.
The cheeky little devil.
You bastard!
You piled them there while we turned
our attention to watching the moon.
You are nothing but a cheater!
A rotten human cheater!
Show me in the handbook where it
says I can't do something like that.
All you told me was to lose means to die,
and that was the only rule in this fight.
When it comes to my survival,
I don't care who I offend.
Beep, beep.
Hiya!
Yah!
The human's getting close
to the column! Yah! Get him!
Don't let him get him!
JoJo will be the first one to the hammer.
Yes yes yes yes I can't wait
to have you in my grasp.
I've got you you're mine damn I'm going
a lot faster than I thought I was!
Now stay there Jojo it snagged
my ring couldn't have predicted
that great that was lucky now
the The fight is in the bag.
I've got this.
You can have the hammer.
That was my plan from the very beginning.
I see Wamuu has a plan in mind.
Let me see it now.
You're fighting genius.
A little oil up here, add some pommel.
I've got a little medicine
for you right here, Wamuu.
Wamu's starting to lose speed.
It's not a race.
They are in a fight to the death.
The keys to winning are
tactics and strategy.
The right weaponry.
Control of the environment.
All right then.
I'll just slow down and introduce him
to my little friend here, the hammer.
Jojo, listen, you mustn't
slow down anymore.
Since you're the one with the
hammer, I'll just get something else.
So, Wamu, are you ready to see
exactly what this thing can do?
Then here we go!
Look there!
He was so happy with his hammer
at first, but not anymore!
He sure plans ahead better than I do!
Hurry up!
Go faster and get away from him, Jojo!
Too late!
So now, you will no
longer have your chariot.
Down already?
Things seem to be over a bit early.
He might want to rethink his plan.
Jojo!
The probability of him being
trampled by my vampire horses is 90%.
The chance of him attempting
to break left is 5%,
and breaking to the right is 5%.
So now then, what is our little
human warrior going to do?
My hammer.
Where is my hammer?
He wants his hammer?
Did he hit his head too hard?
That hammer's not going to save you now!
Jojo must not dodge.
If he does, Wamuu will stop and
finish him with his divine sandstorm.
But what Jojo did was grab the hammer
and head straight for Wamuu's chariot.
Well done, Jojo. Great thinking.
That's exactly right.
What?
He struck the yoke midway
between the horses.
As the horses ran on, Jojo used the hammer's
force to launch himself into the sky.
That move was unbelievable.
The hammer's life kept him from being
trampled under the hooves of the horses.
How was that?
And now for that big hammer
whack you worked so hard to earn.
He's gone.
Where'd he go?
You can clearly see that Wamu
is a step ahead of his quarry.
Wait, that's right!
These fellas can hide themselves
inside other creatures!
Ha-ha!
That was close!
His boot came off his foot!
That boot saved him!
If he only had on some
other kind of footwear!
I've got luck on my side!
For example, the way the handle of
that hammer got caught on my ring.
Luck helps with effectiveness.
Now let's take a look at your situation.
Wamu, your own power has trapped
you inside of that horse.
That's not very lucky.
And here we go.
A little hum on for you and the
horse you rode in on. You fool.
You don't see the trap.
Careful, Jojo.
You need to keep an arm's leg from him.
Now that Wamuu has merged with that
horse, he's free to use his hands!
without worrying about vibration or speed.
Which means, then...
No one has survived a
direct hit by that attack.
Caesar couldn't.
And now you will taste Divine Sandstorm!
Even if it lasted only the
distance of half a lap,
it was a battle filled with
many twists and surprises.
But in the end, Wamu proved the
superiority of both his thinking?
and his fighting prowess.
I think the next battle is going
to be quite a test of will.
Truly, it is not my
preference to fight a woman.
Wamu dislikes it even more.
Notwithstanding, all users of
Hamon must be done away with.
Drink that.
It will provide a painless death thanks
that's quite considerate
of you but Jojo seems
to be a little less dead than you thought
huh Lord course look
out there in the arena
It can't be
Lord Wamu's arms They look
like they're about to fall off
Madness
How could this have
possibly happened to me?
What's wrong?
What is happening to Wamu out there?
Look! There! It's Jojo! He's alive!
He's moving!
He's not even hurt!
Well, I apparently managed
to survive once again.
But Wamuu hit him directly with
his divine sandstorm attack.
How could he?
Directly?
Jojo was cunning enough to make
it look like it was a direct hit.
He is an absolute genius at
trickery and misdirection.
But I'm not sure I should be
giving him praise for that.
Take a close look at Wamuu's arms.
Oh, wait, now I see.
He wrapped the reins around Wamuu's
arms after filling them with Hamon.
Wamuu's divine sandstorm
was short-circuited.
Wamuu was already sticking
one hand out of the horse.
He was going to try to
use his divine sandstorm.
However, in order to do so, I knew he'd
have to stick his other hand out too.
And I had the perfect
counter for that move.
Lord Wamu's face! Look at him!
He's in agony! See that?
He doesn't seem to know where he's going!
His eyes are vacant!
What should we do?
It's the second lap!
But what's going to happen?
Lord Wamu can't hold a weapon like that!
Is it even possible for him to fight?
It's not a surprise.
Right in mid-attack, Wamu was
struck with a lethal dose of Homo.
The confidence built up over
millennia of triumph has crumbled.
The quiet, calm intensity his
victories gave him has vanished.
A tragic shock for him.
But it matters not at all.
Put out the next set of
weapons and do it now!
Lord Kars has given the order.
When he speaks, we must obey!
For the second lap, both
warriors will receive crossbows.
Each comes with ammunition for two shots.
The first warrior there has the
choice of the small or large bow.
What's this now?
There's two weapons.
There's a large one and
another that's smaller.
Lisa, Lisa, this is what's
going through your thoughts now.
Wamuu's mind is in no
condition to entertain a fight.
So why then would Kars be
deploying these new weapons,
and with such apparent confidence?
It's very unsettling, is it not?
Well, the reason is that at his core, Wamuu
is a warrior of legendary mental power.
The very best athletes use a psychological
technique called the Switch Comeback.
When these champions are brought low by
the pressure of shock, failure, or fear,
they can flip a mental
switch and bring out their
fighting spirit for one
last Herculean effort.
Desperate times call for desperate
measures, and Wamuu will win at any cost!
No, I don't believe it!
Did he really just do that? What?
No, Lord Wamuu!
Look, his eyes are gone!
He poked out his eyes!
I foolishly relied on my eyes
because I was able to see,
and Jojo exploited my weakness.
Now I will use this horn to see things
outlined in wind instead of light.
He flipped the switch by removing
his eyes from the equation.
Now he is once again
psychologically invincible.
He senses the wind with
that horn on his forehead.
He sees air better than he did light. Huh?
What is that supposed to be?
That's not going to have any effect on me.
Because of you, I lost my friend Caesar.
Try any trick you want.
I'll do whatever it takes
to finish the fight.
Jojo, which crossbow will you take?
Yeah, which one?
You need to ask.
You know the answer to that.
The large one, you stupid morons.
Power is what I want.
You gotta admit that one does have power.
Yeah, lots of power.
Oh, come on!
I can't even draw this thing.
It's so tight, I can't get the
string to go anywhere at all.
You like it?
You got greedy, didn't you?
Even a normal crossbow takes a huge
amount of strength to draw back.
You had to have the big one, huh?
That's what greed gets you.
I will use the first ball to
paint a picture of the wind.
Now that I know what the range
is, the next shot will not miss.
How am I supposed to defend myself
if I can't shoot this thing?
Lord Wobble, shoot him!
Blow us the smithereens!
Let us snack on whatever
small pieces remain.
Right, just as I thought.
The wind stirred up by these fires makes
it hard for him to figure out where I am.
This is the spot.
That's an error.
Underestimating Wamul.
What?
Lord Wamuu's pointing away from Jojo!
He's turned this way!
He's aiming at us!
Jojo is staying on the
opposite side from Wamuu,
thinking to shelter behind the flame.
Actually, he has only served
to point out his position.
I see what Wamuu is doing.
He's banking it like it's a billion shot!
He hit me from behind!
I was examining the terrain
while we were circling.
I had to find the proper wall
placement to use as a weapon.
I can't breathe.
The ball lost some of its momentum.
So it did not pierce Jojo's skin.
But he's spitting up a lot of blood.
Which would then betoken some injury.
Finish him now, Wamu!
But remember how wily and
full of tricks Jojo is.
Be on your guard.
Has he set another trap?
When I hit the ground, the
impact cocked my crossbow.
I can't let him know that.
I can't kill him from this distance.
Closer, a little closer.
That's it.
He did.
Ahhhhhhhhhh! Hm?
Huh, almost made it.
His aim was off though,
unfortunately for him.
But I really must commend him for
staying in the fight until the very last.
It's over, Jojo. No! Stay away!
Don't come any closer!
Go away!
Leave me alone! Please!
I just can't take anymore!
You've got to spam me!
Hm. Shameful. Look at him!
The sniveling coward's throwing rocks!
He's just a pathetic loser!
Try to go down like a man,
you disgusting little worm!
Listen, Wamuu.
Here is the very next thing that
will come out of your mouth.
Don't you dare dishonor
our battle here, Jojo.
Want some more?
That bother you?
You know that a bat could
simply fly right between
all those rocks and
avoid every little piece.
Why can't you avoid them like that, Wamuu?
An iron ball!
It showed up out of nowhere!
You bastard.
I guess the human just
took you down again.
You see, I banked the shot
just like you did earlier.
The arena went silent.
Not one individual made a sound.
There wasn't even a moan.
Wamu's injury peered out like the
sneering face of a jack-o'-lantern.
The iron ball carried with
it a small amount of hamon.
The wound began to fester.
Wamu's damaged arms grew even worse.
No more divine sandstorms, now or ever.
I've got to try to breathe again.
Get my hormone in balance.
You're trying a kick after faking a fall?
All right, if you still
think you can do this.
REBUFF OVERDRIVE!
It's over!
Wamuu won't be getting up again!
How can this be?
What has become of the great Wamuu?
The mighty warrior is no more.
12,000 years of victory, reduced to this.
His arms, his arms are gone.
It is not Uamo's way
to give up an easy win.
My wounds are only to flesh.
My losses are a path to ability.
I will use all of these
things for victory.
His arms.
He threw them using his chest wound.
They've grabbed Jojo and are choking him.
What's this?
I can't breathe.
I can't gather my hormone.
What's going on?
That wind, it's flowing towards Wamuu.
The wind obeys me.
This is my ultimate mastery!
Ultimate mastery?
No, you shouldn't!
Stop it, Wamuu!
It must not be done!
The wind is going into those pipes!
Ultimate mastery, atmospheric rift!
Remember you,
just in the wind,
we'll charge the view of this atmosphere,
cold at morning, driving through the sun,
and even in the valley, in and around
the lake, models come out of the sky,
they stand there.
One mile over, we'll be
there and we'll see you?
Ten two summers, we'll be
there and I'm laughing too!
Twenty four before my love, you'll see.
I'll be there with you.
Among the jumping crowd, the eagles
searching down on the ground!
Watching the sliding green, the
silver seas, the men of the land!
You cowardly animals!
No matter the method, utilize
remarkable you crossed a line!
No honor earns you!
No consideration!
This world and all in it belong to me.